<resources>
    <string name="notifyTitle">Prompt</string>
    <string name="gpsNotifyMsg">Current mobile phone scanning Bluetooth needs to open the positioning function</string>
    <string name="setting">Go to settings</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="waiting_permission">waiting for permission granted…</string>

    <string name="ble_connecting">bluetooth connecting</string>
    <string name="connection_failed">connection failed</string>
    <string name="connection_succeed">connection succeed</string>
    <string name="ble_disconnect">bluetooth disconnected</string>
    <string name="find_device">new device discovered, please open the list to view</string>

    <string name="help_desc">using help</string>
    <string name="locate">get location</string>
    <string name="mode_change">occlusion mode change</string>
    <string name="device_list">device list</string>
    <string name="device_image">device image</string>

    <string name="initial_list">No hidden device has been found yet. Please wait patiently</string>
    <string name="you_chose">you chose: </string>
    <string name="starting_point">starting point</string>

    <string name="help_info">Automatically connect raspberry pie and send VIO data when this application is opened. Please turn on bluetooth for raspberry pie to ensure a smooth connection\n
        \nPlease walk around the house with this device and raspberry pie in hand to collect RSSI and VIO information\n
        \nThe new device found will be updated in the list and display a sphere in the corresponding position. Please wait patiently\n
        \nClick on the list item and the purple arrow will show you the direction\n
        \nClick the occlusion button to switch the occlusion mode to make AR objects integrate into the real environment/ignore reality occlusion and display completely\n
        \nAR needs to locate according to the points with obvious features. Try not to make the picture taken by the camera too monotonous (for example, a large solid color wall / floor, occlusion lens causes pure black) or shake violently. Please use it in a well-lit environment.
    </string>
</resources>
