<resources>
    <string name="notifyTitle">Prompt</string>
    <string name="open_bluetooth">Please open bluetooth</string>
    <string name="gpsNotifyMsg">Current mobile phone scanning Bluetooth needs to open the positioning function</string>
    <string name="setting">Go to settings</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="waiting_permission">waiting for permission granted…</string>

    <string name="ble_connecting">bluetooth connecting</string>
    <string name="connection_failed">connection failed</string>
    <string name="connection_succeed">connection succeed</string>
    <string name="ble_disconnect">bluetooth disconnected</string>
    <string name="find_device">new device discovered, please open the list to view</string>

    <string name="help_desc">using help</string>
    <string name="tips_desc">tips</string>
    <string name="mode_change">occlusion mode change</string>
    <string name="device_list">device list</string>
    <string name="device_image">device image</string>

    <string name="initial_list">No hidden device has been found yet. Please wait patiently</string>
    <string name="back_to_start">back to base point</string>
    <string name="type_camera">camera</string>
    <string name="type_doorbell">smart doorbell</string>
    <string name="type_plug">smart plug</string>
    <string name="type_scamera">small camera</string>
    <string name="type_unknown">unknown type</string>
    <string name="coordinate">coordinate: </string>
    <string name="you_chose">you chose: </string>
    <string name="starting_point">starting point</string>

    <string name="help_info">
        This app will automatically connect to Raspberry PI and send location information after opening. \n
        \nPlease make sure that the connection is successful and walk around the house with both devices in hand\n
        \nThe newly discovered device will update in the list and display a sphere in the corresponding position, please wait patiently for\n
        \nClick on the object in the list and the purple arrow will show you the way
        </string>
    <string name="tip1">
        AR needs to be located according to points with obvious features.\n
        \nTry not to make the camera shot too monotonous (such as: large solid color wall/floor, block the lens resulting in pure black picture);\n
        \nReduce violent shaking; Please use in a well-lit environment.
    </string>
    <string name="tip2">
        Click the Occlusion button to switch occlusion mode, so that AR objects: \n
        \nintegrate into the real environment or ignore the real environment (complete display)
    </string>
    <string name="tip3">
        The first six digits of the MAC address are organizational unique identifiers (OUI). \n
        \nYou can find out the manufacturer of the hidden device by looking at \n
        \nhttps://standards-oui.ieee.org/oui/oui.txt, better than nothing.
    </string>
    <string name="tip4">
        AR function of this software is developed by AR Foundation of Unity3D, based on ARCore framework of Google.
    </string>
    <string name="tip5">
        The device coordinates displayed follow Unity3D, a left-handed, Y-Up coordinate system. \n
        With right x, before z and y above.
    </string>
    <string name="tip6">
        We know the location of the device through ARCore\'s motion tracking feature. \n
        \nMotion tracking is based on the Visual Inertial Odometry (VIO) technology,\n
        \nwhich analyzes the image and acceleration sensor information to locate the motion.
    </string>
    <string name="tip7">
        Due to the combination of camera and acceleration analysis, AR positioning will fail in several cases: \n
        \n1. Tracking in a moving environment: for example, when a user uses ARCore on a moving elevator, \n
        the data obtained by IMU includes not only the acceleration of the user but also the acceleration of the elevator, which will lead to tracking failure. \n
        \n2. Tracking dynamic environment: For example, when the user takes a picture of the fluctuating water surface, \n
        the image information obtained from the camera is unstable, which will lead to the error of feature point extraction. \n
        \n3. Thermal drift: Both the camera and IMU are temperature sensitive devices, there may be a problem of equipment\n
        heating during the use of the equipment, which will affect the accuracy of the color information obtained by the camera\n
        and the acceleration information measured by the IMU, and then the AR object will drift.
    </string>
    <string name="tip8">
        Update plan:\n
        \n- Bluetooth custom scan and connection;
        \n- Beautify device location information;
        \n- Displays the distance between the selected hidden device and the user in real time.
    </string>
    <string name="one_more_tip">next tip</string>
    <string name="round">You\'ve already seen one round</string>
</resources>
